learnphotoshopnow.com 2013-07-27

# Privacy Policy

****

**OUR PRIVACY POLICY**

LearnPhotoshopNow.com is committed to protecting the privacy of our online visitors. We collect information from online visitors who ask to be on our newsletter mailing list and/or receive periodic email announcements or free reports. Anyone who wishes can choose to be removed from our mailing list at any time. Each email will always contain a simple unsubscribe link.

All online visitor data collected by LearnPhotoshopNow.com is protected against unauthorized access. We will not sell, trade, or give your personal information to other companies or organizations.

**

Children’s Privacy

**

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If we learn that we have personal information on a child under the age of 13, we will delete that information from our systems. LearnPhotoshopNow.com encourages parents to go online with their kids. Here are a few tips to help make a child's online experience safer:

* Teach kids never to give personal information, unless supervised by a parent or responsible adult. Includes name, address, phone, school, etc. 
* Know the sites your kids are visiting and which sites are appropriate. 
* Look for Web site privacy policies. Know how your child's information is treated. 

Check out the FTC's site: http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/conline/edcams/kidzprivacy/index.html for more tips on protecting children's privacy online. 

**Contacting Us.**

We can be reached by contacting: LearnPhotoshopNow.com,  Email: LearnPhotoshopNow@sp8.net
